<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="test_address" translatable="false">100 n main st, providence, RI, 02903</string>

    <string name="app_name">VotingInformationProject</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>
    <string name="activity.home.go_button">GO</string>
    <string name="activity.home.select_contact_button">Contacts</string>
    <string name="activity.home.select_location_button">Location</string>
    <string name="activity.vip.tab">Voting Info Project</string>
    <string name="activity.title.about">About This App</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="error.no_phone">Phone not installed</string>
    <string name="error.no_email">Email client not installed</string>
    <string name="error.no_browser">Web browser not installed</string>

    <!-- Tab Bar Strings -->
    <string name="bottom.navigation.title.ballot">Ballot</string>
    <string name="bottom.navigation.title.polls">Polling Sites</string>
    <string name="bottom.navigation.title.details">Details</string>

    <!-- Directions origin dialog -->
    <string name="activity.vip.tab.directions_origin_prompt">Where do you want directions from?</string>

    <array name="activity_vip_tab_directions_origin_options">
        <item>Entered Address</item>
        <item>Current Location</item>
    </array>

    <!-- Prompt to enable location services -->
    <string name="activity.vip.tab.enable_location_services_prompt">Could not find current location.  Enable location services now?</string>

    <!-- Home View Strings -->
    <string name="fragment.home.text_view_brand_name">VOTING INFORMATION PROJECT</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.text_view_voting_info">Voting Information</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.text_view_getting_started">Enter Your Address</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.text_view_election_spinner_text">Pick an Election</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.text_view_party_spinner_text">There are partisan contests in this election. Choose a party to view.</string>
    <string name="activity_home_status_loading">Loading data…</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.error_address_not_found">Looks like we can\'t find your address. Please check that it\'s right and try again.</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.error_parsing_address">We couldn\'t read the address you entered.  Please check that it\'s right and try again</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.error_no_election_for_address">We couldn\'t find any election information for the address you entered.</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.error_no_address">Please check that you\'ve got an address entered and try again.</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.error_unknown">We weren\'t able to get results for the address you entered.  Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.error_no_internet">Cannot connect to the Internet.  Please check your connection.</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.go_button_accessibility_description">Go to search results.</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.select_contact_button_description">Open contacts to select a contact address.</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.select_location_button_description">Use current location to search for elections.</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.search_button_description">Search for results.</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.election_spinner_description">Please pick an election"</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.party_spinner_description">Please pick a party:</string>
    <string name="fragment.home.all_parties">All Parties</string>

    <!-- Feedback Strings -->
    <string name="feedback.link">Report an Error</string>
    <string name="feedback.loading">Loading feedback form…</string>

    <!-- Election View Strings -->
    <string name="fragment.ballot.list.header.contests">Contests</string>

    <!-- Contest Detail Strings -->
    <string name="contest.header.details">Contest Details</string>
    <string name="contest.label.type">Type</string>
    <string name="contest.label.office">Office</string>
    <string name="contest.label.number_elected">Number Elected</string>
    <string name="contest.label.number_voting_for">Number Voting For</string>
    <string name="contest.label.ballot_placement">Ballot Placement</string>
    <string name="contest.header.candidate_list">Candidates</string>

    <!-- Candidate Details Strings -->
    <string name="candidate.details_header">Candidate Details</string>
    <string name="candidate.social_header">Social Media Channels</string>
    <string name="candidate.no_name">No Name Available</string>
    <string name="candidate.no_party">No Listed Affiliation</string>
    <string name="candidate.details_none">No Candidate Details Available</string>

    <!-- Accessibility descriptions for images -->
    <string name="social.channel.description.youtube">Visit YouTube channel</string>
    <string name="social.channel.description.twitter">Visit Twitter feed</string>
    <string name="social.channel.description.facebook">Visit FaceBook page</string>
    <string name="social.channel.description.google_plus">Visit Google Plus page</string>

    <string name="accessibility.description.email">Send email</string>
    <string name="accessibility.description.phone">Call phone number</string>
    <string name="accessibility.description.website">Visit website</string>
    <string name="accessibility.description.candidate">Candidate picture</string>

    <!-- Election Detail Strings -->
    <string name="details.body.header.state_administration">State Administration</string>
    <string name="details.body.header.local_administration">Local Administration</string>
    <string name="details.no_messages_found">No election administration information found for this election.</string>

    <!-- Election Links Strings -->
    <string name="details.section.header.links">Election Information Websites</string>
    <string name="details.label.election_info_url">Election Information</string>
    <string name="details.label.voter_registration_url">Voter Registration Information</string>
    <string name="details.label.voter_registration_confirmation_url">Voter Registration Confirmation</string>
    <string name="details.label.absentee_voting_url">Absentee Voter Information</string>
    <string name="details.label.voting_location_finder_url">Voting Location Finder Information</string>
    <string name="details.label.ballot_info_url">Ballot Information</string>
    <string name="details.label.election_rules_url">Election Rules</string>
    <string name="details.label.voter_services">Voter Services</string>
    <string name="details.label.hours_of_operation">Hours of Operation</string>
    <string name="details.label.correspondence_address">Correspondence Address</string>
    <string name="details.label.physical_address">Physical Address</string>
    <string name="details.label.election_officials">Election Officials</string>
    <!-- End Election Detail Strings -->


    <!-- Locations strings -->
    <string name="locations.button.list_map">map</string>
    <string name="locations.list.label.all_sites">All Sites</string>
    <string name="locations.list.label.early_voting">Early Voting</string>
    <string name="locations.list.label.polling_sites">Polling Sites</string>
    <string name="locations.list.label.drop_off">Drop Off</string>
    <string name="locations.list.none_found">No locations found.</string>
    <string name="locations.distance_suffix_imperial">mi.</string>
    <string name="locations.distance_suffix_metric">km</string>

    <!-- Locations map strings -->
    <string name="locations.map.label.user_address">User Address</string>
    <string name="locations.map.label.user_location">Current Location</string>
    <string name="locations.map.label.election_administration_body">Election Administration Body Location</string>
    <string name="locations.map.error.play_services_unavailable">Google Play services are unavailable.  Cannot show locations map, distances, or directions.</string>
    <string name="locations.map.error.geocode">Unable to find location for that address.</string>
    <string name="locations.map.label.polling_location_hours">Hours:</string>
    <string name="locations.map.error.polling_location_hours_not_found">Hours of operation not found for this location.</string>

    <!-- Directions list strings -->
    <string name="directions.label.walk_button">Walk</string>
    <string name="directions.label.bike_button">Bike</string>
    <string name="directions.label.transit_button">Transit</string>
    <string name="directions.label.drive_button">Drive</string>
    <string name="directions.label.open_in_maps_button">Open in Google Maps</string>
    <string name="directions.error.no_directions_found">No directions found.</string>
    <string name="directions.error.no_origin">Could not find origin point for directions.</string>
    <string name="directions.loading">Loading directions…</string>

    <!-- About App strings -->
    <string name="about.app.title">About This App</string>
    <string name="about.app.description">The Voting Information Project (VIP) works to connect voters with the essential information needed to cast their ballot, such as where to vote and what is on the ballot. It is a project between The Pew Charitable Trusts, Google, and the states. Launched in 2008, VIP works with state and local election officials to provide official election information to citizens through a variety of means, including the Google Civic Information API. This app one of the many made available through VIP, ensuring official election information is accessible to voters before and on Election Day.</string>
    <string name="about.title.terms">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="about.terms.description">Effective Date: 6/11/14\n\nThe Voting Information Project (\"VIP\"), a project of The Pew Charitable Trusts (\"Pew\"), provides users with official election and polling place information, collected from and verified by state and local election officials.\n\nVIP is nonpartisan online voter resource, partnering with organizations and election officials committed to leveraging technology to provide official voting information to voters where they look for it most. By using the VIP Application (the \"App\") and the services offered through the App, including, but not limited to the VIP state feeds (collectively with the App, the \"Use\"), you agree to be bound by these Terms of Use and the terms of the Voting Information Project Privacy Policy, as in effect at the time you access the App.\n\nUse Guidelines and Prohibitions\nYou agree to Use the services solely for personal, not-for-profit or educational purposes.  You agree not to Use the services to: (a) violate any law, or (b) disobey any requirements, procedures, policies or regulations of networks connected to the services, or interfere with or disrupt the services, the App or servers or networks connected to the App.\n\nBy accessing the App or any other service provided through the App, you agree to abide by the following standards of conduct. You agree that you will not, nor will you authorize or facilitate any attempt by another person, to use the App or any service provided through the App to:\n\n1)Attempt to decipher, decompile, disassemble, or reverse-engineer any of the software comprising or in any way making up a part of the App;\n2)Transmit any Content that includes files or hyperlinks which contain viruses, worms, Trojan horses, spyware, malware, or any other destructive features, or any data otherwise intended to interfere with the proper working of the App; or\n3)Violate any federal, state, local, or international law or regulation.\n\nAccessing (or attempting to access) any of our resources by any means other than through the means we provide, is strictly prohibited. You specifically agree not to access (or attempt to access) any of our resources through any automated, unethical or unconventional means.\n\nOwnership and License\nAll right, title, and interest in and to VIP and VIP content are and will remain the exclusive property of Pew and its licensors.\n\nPew hereby grants to you a nonexclusive, term, limited, irrevocable, royalty-free, worldwide license (the \"License\") to install, execute, load, operate, display, customize, and otherwise use the App solely for personal, not-for-profit or educational purposes, subject to the restrictions set forth in these Terms of Use.\n\nIndemnification\nBy using this the App, you agree to indemnify, hold harmless, and defend Pew and its employees and agents from any claims, damages, losses, liabilities, and all costs and expenses of defense, including but not limited to, attorneysí fees, resulting directly or indirectly from a claim by you or a third-party that arises in connection with: (i) your violation of any term of these Terms of Use; (ii) your violation of any third-party right, including without limitation any copyright, property, or privacy right; or (iii) any claim that any sharing of information caused damage to a third-party. This defense and indemnification obligation will survive these Terms of Use and your use of the App.\n\nLimitation of Liability\nAll use of VIP and VIP content is provided \"as is\" and at your own risk.\n\nPew will not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or exemplary loss or damages which may be incurred by you as a result of using our resources, or as a result of any charges, data loss or corruption, cancellation, loss of access, or downtime to the full extent that applicable limitation of liability laws apply.\n\nPrivacy\nVIP does not collect any personally identifiable information and does not collect or distribute any information entered by a user, including address information.  You understand that any information provided by you or collected by Pew in connection with your Use will be used in the manner described in these Terms of Service and in the VIP Privacy Policy, such privacy policy being incorporated into and made a part of these Terms of Service by this reference.\n\nJurisdiction and Choice of Law\nThese Terms of Service, and any disputes arising from or relating to the conduct covered by the Terms of Service, are governed by the laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania.  You hereby submit to the exclusive jurisdiction, including waiving any objection to personal jurisdiction, of the courts of the Philadelphia, Pennsylvania without regards to any principles of conflicts of laws and the United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods.  Those who choose to access the Services from locations outside of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania do so on their own initiative contrary to the terms of these Terms of Service, and are responsible for compliance with local laws if and to the extent local laws are applicable.\n\nQuestions\n</string>
    <string name="about.title.privacy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="about.privacy.description">Effective Date: 6/11/14\n\nThe Voting Information Project (\"VIP\"), a project of The Pew Charitable Trusts (\"Pew\"), values your privacy and does not require that users enter personally identifiable information or information about an individual that could reasonably be used to identify that individual. This Privacy Policy (\"Privacy Policy\") describes the types of information that VIP gathers from you when you use our App and associated services (the \"Service\").    Our Service does not require you to provide your first and last name, residential address, telephone number, and email address. When accessing the Service, you are only required to provide an address to obtain election information for that address.\n\nBy accessing the Service, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Service. Each time you use our Service, the current version of the Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, whenever you use our Service, you should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the top) and review any changes since the last version. This Privacy Policy is applicable to all users of the Service.\n\nFurther, you acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of our Terms of Service and by accessing or using our Service, you agree to be bound by the Terms of Service. If you do not agree to our Terms of Service, do not access or use our Service.\n\nIn addition to collecting an address from you for election information purposes, VIP may also collect certain information automatically for analytic purposes, including, but not limited to, using cookies (small piece of data stored in the user\'s device) and anonymous identifiers when you interact with the Services.  Any use of cookies – or of other tracking tools – by the Service or by the owners of third party services used by this App, unless stated otherwise, is for analytic purposes or serves to anonymously identify users and remember their preferences for the purpose of providing the Service requested.  Pew shares the limited information that it collects with third party service providers, such as Google, to assist with rendering the Service.  Use of your information by these third parties is governed by their privacy policy.\n\nVIP employs industry standard security measures to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information used by VIP. VIP has added \"Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure\" (HTTPS), a widely used communications protocol for secure communication over a computer network, with especially wide deployment on the Internet.  It adds the security capabilities of SSL/TLS to standard HTTP communications.\n\nVIP contains links to third party sites, partnering organizations, applications and services not operated by us. These links are provided as a service and do not imply any endorsement by Pew of the activities or content of these sites, applications or services nor any association with their operators. Pew is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party including websites or services directly linked to our Service. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party site that you link from our Service.\n\nPew reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. If Pew makes any material changes to this Privacy Policy or the way that Pew uses, shares or collects personally identifiable information, Pew will notify you by revising the \"Effective Date\" at the top of this Privacy Policy or prominently posting an announcement of the changes through the Service prior to the new policy taking effect.  Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy after notice of such changes have been communicated. Pew encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are familiar with current practices.\n\nIf you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices please contact us as follows:\n\nBy emailing the Privacy Department at info@votinginfoproject.org\n\n By mail post to:\n\n Privacy Department\nVoting Information Project\nElection Initiatives\n901 E St. NW\nWashington, DC 20004–2008</string>
    <string name="about.title.legal_notices">Legal Notices</string>
    <string name="about.description.legal_notices">BSD 3-Clause License\n\nCopyright © 2014, The Pew Charitable Trust\n\nAll rights reserved.\n\nRedistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:\n\nRedistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n\nRedistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\n\nNeither the name of The Pew Charitable Trusts nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.\n\nTHIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n\n</string>
    <string name="about.title.mail_only">This election is mail only.</string>
    <string name="about.description.mail_only">Your upcoming election is mail-only. Please contact your local election official to learn more about how to receive and return your ballot.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
