<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:id="@+id/contest_referendum_scrollview"
    style="@style/match_width_match_height">

    <LinearLayout
        style="@style/wrap_width_wrap_height"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/contest_title"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            style="@style/fragment_header" />

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/contest_subtitle"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            style="@style/fragment_subheader" />

        <TextView
            android:padding="16dp"
            android:id="@+id/contest_referendum_text"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:textColor="@color/dark_text"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            tools:text="Pierce County General Services Building\n\nShould Pierce County proceed with financing and construction of the proposed new Pierce County General Services Building on County-owned property in the City of Tacoma as authorized by Pierce County Council Ordinance No. 2015-2s?\n\n[] Yes\n[] No"
            />

        <TextView
            android:padding="16dp"
            android:id="@+id/contest_referendum_pro"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:textColor="@color/dark_text"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:autoLink="web"
            tools:text="Please vote yes to support the cost saving plan to consolidate 19 government programs into one location. No more wasted time going to different places for county services. Already approved by the County Council, the $127M public/private partnership consolidates programs currently housed in 14 locations. \n\nFact: no tax increases are necessary. The project saves taxpayers money by ending expensive leases and reducing 38 positions that would be redundant in one location. Fact: the fully furnished costs are locked in - with the prices guaranteed by the builder. Fact: maintaining existing leases, older facilities and redundant positions will costs tens of millions more than a new, centralized building over 30 years (including interest). \n\nThis pencils out. One new building is more cost effective than renting numerous buildings. Don't be misled by scare tactics and political shenanigans. Saving money + customer service = fiscally responsible governing. Get the facts: www.pierceountywa.org/GSB\n\nREBUTTAL OF ARGUMENT AGAINST:\n\nTransparency: The county publicly announced this proposal two years ago. It's been discussed at over 30 public meetings. The County Council voted 6-1to spend $1 million to design the building on land the county already owns. Like a home mortgage, the fixed 30 year lease saves money for community priorities like public safety. Critics refuse to acknowledge that consolidating operations makes fiscal sense. Please don't let their false claims block a more efficient government.\n\nFOR MORE INFORMATION:\n\nhttps://weiapplets.sos.wa.gov/myvote/onlinevotersguide/Measures?electionid=…"
            />

        <TextView
            android:padding="16dp"
            android:id="@+id/contest_referendum_con"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:textColor="@color/dark_text"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:autoLink="web"
            tools:text="The current plan lacks transparency and public input from all of Pierce County The building's authorization was narrowly approved by 4-3 vote. The full council doesn't support this project, neither should you. Since July 2013 building costs have doubled to over $230 million. \n\nA rushed plan to spend over $230 million without transparency or a public vote Projected cost savings and financing plans are based on wishful thinking. The contract allows significant lease increases which could drain County funds from other local projects and community programs. Jobs will be eliminated to pay for this 30 year project. \n\nBuilding costs and poor planning cause project spending to spiral out of control Current leases for 30 years cost approximately $100 million. The new building is estimated to cost over $230 million. Current annual leases total $3.2 million; the proposed new lease is estimated at more than $8.1 million per year. We can't bet on imaginary savings to make up the difference. \n\nYour No vote sends an important message to Pierce County government to start over Stop this fiasco. Costs were underestimated; benefits are overstated. We must start over with a public review committee that considers project alternatives, saving taxpayers millions. Vote No.\n\nREBUTTAL OF ARGUMENT FOR:\n\nTheir pencil's broken. The true cost is $230 million with interest. This plan has many flaws: traffic, parking, location, high cost and lack of transparency to all of Pierce County. Why is new debt and spending the only answer when existing locations are available that will save taxpayers millions? Ask yourself, why are we laying off our workers so a King County contractor can be paid our tax dollars? Vote No, let's restart this idea.\n\nFOR MORE INFORMATION:\n\nhttps://weiapplets.sos.wa.gov/myvote/onlinevotersguide/Measures?electionid=…"
            />

        <include layout="@layout/feedback_link" />
    </LinearLayout>

</ScrollView>
